保護性 for such complainants.
政府法案，守讀。
政府法案二讀，律政司司長。
二零一七年中醫藥修訂條例草案。
二零一七年成文法雜項規定條例草案。
呢啲嘅資訊或者資源或者有啲問題咧，去解決嘅。多謝主席。
Both these amendments aimed to align the practice in question with other similar arrangements.
二零一七年保護瀕危動植物物種修訂條例草案。
將會被給予同級註冊官一樣的管轄權限和權力。
Parts four and eight of the bill seek to amend the district court ordinance. The amendments are also proposed by the judiciary.
And non-controversial to various ordinances for the purpose of updating or further enhancing development legislation.
主席，我 move that the Statute Law Miscellaneous Provision Bill 2017, the bill, be read the second time. It has been the practice of the Department of Justice (DOJ) to introduce at regular intervals to the Legislative Council a Statute Law Miscellaneous Provision Bill, proposing minor amendments that are largely technical.
The last statute law miscellaneous provision bill was enacted in 2014. The government finds it necessary to introduce another omnibus bill so as to make miscellaneous amendments to various ordinances. The amendments are set out in parts two to nine of the bill. The key elements can be outlined as follows.
Part two of the bill seeks to amend the criminal procedure ordinance and the live television link and video record evidence rules to give the court a discretion to permit complainants of specified sexual offences to give evidence in proceedings by way of a live television link, in order to enhance.
Part three of the bill seeks to clarify the powers of temporary registrars of different ranks appointed to the High Court, the District Court and the Competition Tribunal. The amendments concerned are proposed by the judiciary for the sake of clarity. Through the amendments, temporary registrars appointed such courts and tribunal
Part Four seeks to provide for representation of the Secretary for Justice at the District Court Rules Committee, while the amendment and Part Eight seeks to enable the jurisdiction limit of the amount of claim for costs in costs only proceedings may be amended by resolution of the Legislative Council.
食物及衞生局局長。
主席，我同你二讀二。
efficient manner. With these remarks, I urge members to support the bill. Thank you, President.
mainland， and thereby avoiding confusion of the meaning of the relevant term.
Part seven of the bill amends the Laws Legislative Publication Ordinance 1990 and the Legislation Publication Ordinance to streamline laws compilation and an editorial amendment work.
for at least three months immediately before the day on which the person applies for a certificate of eligibility for admission, but not the date of the applicant's admission as a solicitor, as it currently stands.
現在嘅代議議題係二零一七年成文法雜項規定條例草案預議議讀，按照議事規則辯論終止待續，條例草案交由內務委員會處理。
Part five of the bill seeks to clarify the reference point for the calculation of the period of residence for the purpose of admission as a solicitor in Hong Kong, in response to the proposal of the Law Society of Hong Kong. While with this amendment, a person is required to have resided in Hong Kong.
Part six of the bill amends the English text of the Mainland Judgments Reciprocal Enforcement Ordinance by replacing the references to Basic People's Court or Courts in the Mainland therein by Primary People's Court or Courts, so as to maintain consistency with the English usage of the same term in the.
Part nine of the bill contains miscellaneous and technical amendments to various legislative provisions for different purposes, including to reinstate consequential amendments that were omitted in previous legislative amendment exercise, to formally repeal legislation that has ceased to have effect.
to remove obsolete references, to repeal provisions from certain legal provisions, to achieve consistency in certain expressions, to update a reference to the title of an item of subsidiary legislation, and to make provisions for correcting other minor errors. Mr. President, as I pointed out at the beginning.
beginning of this speech, the bill deals with a number of amendments to various areas in a consolidated manner, which is part of the continuing efforts of the government to collect Hong Kong's legislation. By dealing with the amendments in one go by way of the bill, developing legislative provisions can be further improved in an